# **ATYLA AZFA AL HARITS**

Banjar – Sidaharja Main Road, Ciamis, West Java | +62 812-9889-7305 | azfaalharits25@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/atyla-azfa-al-harits

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a web developer with a strong interest in server-side application development and over 2 years of experience working with PHP frameworks, particularly Laravel. I am often entrusted with leadership roles in campus activities and volunteer programs, demonstrating commitment and dedication in every project I take on.

#### **EXPERIENCES**

## **Mutiara Digital Printing - Technical Assistant (Internship)**

Feb 2022 - Apr 2022

- Head of internship team from SMK Negeri 3 Banjar.
- Assist employees in printing equipment operations.
- Develop a printing shop web application with Codelgniter 4.

## Community Service Desa Serang - Web Developer

Sep 2024 - Nov 2024

Develop a web application named SISKOMDIG for the digital community of Desa Serang.

## **Community Service MTs BPI Baturompe - Web Developer**

Dec 2024

- Head of community service group.
- Develop web application named SITUGAS for monitoring student assignments.

### **PROJECTS**

App Islami TailwindCSS, VueJS, Pinia

A website to see prayer schedules, Al-Quran, Asmaul Husana, daily prayers, and prayer intentions.

Digital Library TailwindCSS, Laravel

A website for librarians to manage books, reading e-books, book borrowers, and fines.

SIMDOKU Laravel, Livewire

A website for document management, such as activity reports, funding applications, and file archives for university.

Islami API TypeScript, ExpressJS

Services that provide APIs such as Asmaul Husna, daily prayers, and prayer intentions.

#### **EDUCATION**

SMK Negeri 3 Banjar - Banjar City

Jun 2020 - May 2023

Software Engineering

Universitas Bina Sarana Informatika - Tasikmalaya City

Sep 2023 - Now

Information Systems

### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Technical Skills: TypeScript, VueJS, Flutter (Basic), PHP (Laravel), AdonisJS, ExpressJS, MySQL.
- Certifications: Database Design & Database Programming with SQL Talent Scouting Academy